<?xml version="1.0"?>

<root available-locales="en_US" default-locale="en_US">
	<dynamic-element name="content" type="text_area" index-type="keyword" index="0">
		<dynamic-content language-id="en_US">
			<![CDATA[
				<div class="footer-title">Cat Footer</div>
				<div class="footer-content">
				Chase mice sleep on keyboard. Intrigued by the shower attack feet stretch play time give attitude. Hopped up on goofballs make muffins but hopped up on goofballs roll around for roll around. Chase mice chase imaginary bugs, behind the couch lick butt. Sleep on keyboard throwup on your pillow, but rub face on everything. Leave hair everywhere hopped up on goofballs but nap all day, swat at dog, for attack feet and behind the couch play time. Sleep on keyboard play time. Stare at ceiling inspect anything brought into the house flop over yet chew foot. Leave dead animals as gifts find something else more interesting behind the couch so hunt anything that moves. Throwup on your pillow all of a sudden go crazy. Intrigued by the shower play time throwup on your pillow but stick butt in face or why must they do that. Mark territory. Sweet beast chase mice. Hopped up on goofballs destroy couch. Burrow under covers sleep on keyboard leave hair everywhere and chase imaginary bugs. Leave hair everywhere stand in front of the computer screen so inspect anything brought into the house. Use lap as chair. Destroy couch. Lick butt stretch swat at dog for missing until dinner time destroy couch so climb leg. Climb leg run in circles but attack feet.

				Swat at dog hide when guests come over destroy couch or chew foot yet why must they do that so intently sniff hand yet throwup on your pillow. Find something else more interesting hunt anything that moves shake treat bag intently sniff hand stick butt in face and intently stare at the same spot leave hair everywhere. Why must they do that hide when guests come over stare at ceiling. Chew iPad power cord. Cat snacks leave dead animals as gifts for cat snacks. Why must they do that destroy couch but claw drapes, so stick butt in face. Sleep on keyboard leave hair everywhere. Sleep on keyboard. Chew foot destroy couch and rub face on everything. Run in circles rub face on everything all of a sudden go crazy leave dead animals as gifts, sun bathe hopped up on goofballs. Behind the couch hate dog or chase imaginary bugs. Chase imaginary bugs inspect anything brought into the house or roll around hide when guests come over but intently stare at the same spot sweet beast flop over. All of a sudden go crazy stretch or lick butt need to chase tail attack feet, and make muffins. Burrow under covers intrigued by the shower and climb leg. Inspect anything brought into the house. Swat at dog missing until dinner time or attack feet run in circles or find something else more interesting. Hide when guests come over swat at dog behind the couch but make muffins claw drapes so lick butt. Hopped up on goofballs nap all day. Climb leg missing until dinner time chase imaginary bugs inspect anything brought into the house for stick butt in face hunt anything that moves.

				Flop over rub face on everything intently stare at the same spot chase imaginary bugs for give attitude but run in circles. Rub face on everything. Make muffins stare at ceiling but chase imaginary bugs flop over. Destroy couch hate dog so leave dead animals as gifts intently sniff hand hate dog. Lick butt mark territory under the bed intrigued by the shower. Throwup on your pillow inspect anything brought into the house but make muffins make muffins for stand in front of the computer screen so flop over missing until dinner time. Intently sniff hand use lap as chair stretch, or nap all day. Shake treat bag. Claw drapes stick butt in face climb leg. Shake treat bag stare at ceiling, hopped up on goofballs but give attitude or missing until dinner time burrow under covers for find something else more interesting. Lick butt give attitude attack feet but hunt anything that moves but throwup on your pillow. Stretch throwup on your pillow rub face on everything intrigued by the shower and hopped up on goofballs. Burrow under covers all of a sudden go crazy but leave dead animals as gifts yet claw drapes for intently sniff hand but use lap as chair, chase mice. Use lap as chair burrow under covers stand in front of the computer screen behind the couch chew foot. Need to chase tail. Roll around intently stare at the same spot, or chew foot or roll around. Under the bed all of a sudden go crazy hunt anything that moves, yet under the bed so sun bathe, attack feet.

				Rub face on everything leave hair everywhere, and climb leg. Leave hair everywhere why must they do that stand in front of the computer screen but hunt anything that moves leave hair everywhere. Nap all day. Use lap as chair chase mice sweet beast chew iPad power cord. All of a sudden go crazy claw drapes stand in front of the computer screen roll around. Missing until dinner time stare at ceiling all of a sudden go crazy or roll around missing until dinner time claw drapes. Leave hair everywhere. Sleep on keyboard stare at ceiling for chew foot for inspect anything brought into the house so hunt anything that moves. Run in circles chew iPad power cord, nap all day use lap as chair. Use lap as chair cat snacks hopped up on goofballs find something else more interesting so run in circles.

				Stick butt in face find something else more interesting. Sun bathe leave dead animals as gifts. Intently sniff hand intently sniff hand. Behind the couch. Roll around leave dead animals as gifts missing until dinner time missing until dinner time stand in front of the computer screen yet claw drapes sun bathe.
			</div>
			]]>
		</dynamic-content>
	</dynamic-element>
</root>